<author lang="en" class="1">
<documents>
<document>My Administration is rebuilding our roads, bridges, and airports, replacing lead pipes, cleaning up pollution, providing affordable high-speed internet to every family in America, and more.

And we’re creating good-paying jobs in the process. https://t.co/UGJJvrjatD</document>
<document>The heart of American capitalism is open and fair competition. 

If companies want to win your business, they have to up their game with better prices and services, and new ideas and products.

I’m working to make the heart of American capitalism work for everyone.</document>
<document>We're making electric vehicles more affordable for families, jumpstarting the first national EV charging network, and bringing in historic investments for EV battery manufacturing here at home.

Electric vehicles are here to stay. https://t.co/I6akwVfdL2</document>
<document>More Americans applied to start new small businesses last year than ever before.
 
We’re building an economy from the bottom up and middle out. And it’s working.</document>
<document>Fair competition is was what made America the wealthiest, most innovative nation in history.
 
Now, imagine if we gave everyone a full and fair chance to get ahead.  That’s what I plan to do.</document>
<document>Shop small today, America! https://t.co/iHlbtFR9hO</document>
<document>More than 32 million small businesses employ almost half of America’s workforce and represent the heart and soul of countless communities.
 
On Small Business Saturday, we celebrate America’s small businesses and their enormous contributions to American life and prosperity.</document>
<document>Under our Administration, 5 million Americans have gained health care coverage.</document>
<document>While we buy gifts for our loved ones, let us be thankful for all the folks working hard to stock shelves, pack boxes, operate cash registers, take orders and deliver packages this holiday season.</document>
<document>Supporting working people is how we continue to build the economy from the bottom up and middle out.

I will also continue fighting for the PRO Act to help workers unionize, and achieve a $15 minimum wage.</document>
</documents>
</author>